<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ConstellationApp</string>
    <string name="instruction_text">Please enter your name</string>
    <string name="instruction_date">Please select your date</string>
    <string name="aries">Aries 3/21-4/19 Astrologers believe that Arians have assertive, pioneering, competitive, and courageous natures. Arians are said to have strong senses of self, and to frequently be selfish. Arians tend to behave in headstrong, impulsive, sometimes foolhardy ways. Although they anger quickly, they get over their anger quickly and do not hold grudges. Astrologers consider many Arians to be natural athletes and to be drawn to physical activity.</string>

    <string name="taurus">Taurus 4/20-5/20 Astrologers consider Taureans to be loyal, stable, conservative, and practical. They are also thought to be patient, affectionate, and good-natured people. However, their tempers can erupt dramatically if they are pushed beyond their limits. Astrologers believe Taureans are home-loving and tend to have deep sentimental attachments to people, things, and places. They also can be jealous and possessive. Astrologers do not consider Taureans to be fond of change, making the typical Taurus both reliable and committed, as well as inflexible.</string>

    <string name="gemini">Gemini 5/21-6/21 According to astrologers, Geminis tend to be quick-witted, changeable, talkative, versatile, and sometimes crafty or mischievous. Geminis are known for their ability to express themselves, and are witty, clever, and often well-read. They usually have something to say about everything. Astrologers believe that typical Geminis have highly developed intellects, and that they place greater importance on learning than on emotional or practical issues. However, they consider Geminis to be so clever that they can give the impression of deep emotion or of the practicality of their desires.</string>

    <string name="cancer">Cancer 6/22-7/22 Astrologers consider Cancerians to be nurturing, emotional, sensitive, conservative, and home-loving. Due to the sign\'s association with the moon, Cancerians often have widely fluctuating moods. Astrologers say Cancerians are artistic, have vivid imaginations, and have highly developed memories. Like people born under other water signs, Cancerians are thought to be much more aware of how they feel than what they think.</string>

    <string name="leo">Leo 7/23-8/22 Astrologers believe that Leos have regal, self-centered, generous, and warm-hearted natures. Leos are said to be protective of people close to them, especially children and those who are weak. They also have a strong need to be the center of attention, and may be surprisingly sensitive. Astrologers think that Leos tend to be inordinately fond of praise and can be swayed by flattery. They consider Leos to be creative and dramatic. Leos also have strong organizational skills and make natural leaders.</string>

    <string name="virgo">Virgo 8/23-9/22 Astrologers believe that Virgoans are practical, no-nonsense people. They like to talk and are good communicators, but prefer to put their words to practical use. Thus they are not very interested in idle conversation, and they can be shy. The typical Virgoan also has a tendency to be critical. According to astrologers, Virgoans often have a great concern for health and hygiene. They also like to be well-groomed and keep their surroundings very tidy.</string>

    <string name="libra">Libra 9/23-10/23 According to astrologers, Libras have diplomatic, refined, intelligent, thoughtful, warm, and social natures. Because of the sign\'s relationship with the planet Venus (named after the ancient Roman goddess of beauty and love), Libras tend to be romantic and crave relationships. Typical Libras, however, want an idealized meeting of the minds in an atmosphere of civility, refinement, and reasonableness. They do not place as much importance on deep emotional intimacy or physical passion. Libras also enjoy comfort and luxury.</string>

    <string name="scorpio">Scorpio 10/24-11/22 Astrologers consider Scorpios to be energetic, passionate, deep, intuitive, and secretive, with a great deal of self-control. They also believe that Scorpios can be willful, stubborn, and easily made jealous. Scorpios are thought to be keen observers of people, and potentially calculating and manipulative. Seeing more of people\'s deepest motivations than others do, they have a tendency to be cynical. They are sensitive and never forget a hurt or a slight—for the typical Scorpio, forgiveness can be difficult.</string>

    <string name="sagittarius">Sagittarius 11/23-12/21 Astrologers believe that Sagittarians have fun-loving, friendly, philosophical, intellectual, straightforward, and expansive natures. Sagittarians are optimistic, and sometimes have a naive belief that everything will turn out fine despite any obstacles. Good luck often follows typical Sagittarians, and because whatever they need usually comes effortlessly to them, they tend to be generous and willing to share. Sagittarians also value frankness and honesty, and their comments can sometimes be blunt.</string>

    <string name="capricornus">Capricorn 12/22-1/19 According to astrologers, Capricorns have responsible, disciplined, practical, methodical, cautious, serious, and sometimes pessimistic natures. Capricorns believe that anything worth having is worth working hard for, and they assign the highest value to things won through the hardest work. Typical Capricorns are aloof and shy, sometimes even awkward, because they stay so focused on responsibility. To them life is serious business, and they sometimes have difficulty relaxing and having fun. Because of this, Capricorns may be lonely.</string>

    <string name="aquarius">Aquarius 1/20-2/18 Astrologers consider Aquarians to be brilliant, visionary, curious, open-minded, original, independent, and eccentric. Though emotionally detached, they also tend to be friendly and social. According to astrologers, Aquarians have a highly developed sense of social equality and often are attracted to activism or progressive political organizations.</string>

    <string name="pisces">Pisces 2/19-3/20 Astrologers consider Pisceans to be sensitive, emotional, sunny, impressionable, dreamy, creative, psychic, and mystical. Pisceans tend to be idealistic; sometimes the real world gets too harsh and ugly for them. To escape unpleasant realities, some Pisceans retreat into their own dreams and fantasies and become evasive, even deceitful. Others escape productively through charity work, the arts, religion, meditation, and solitude. Pisceans make good listeners, can see different sides of issues, and often have great sympathy for the suffering of others.</string>

</resources>
